kems.net 2016-03-13

# KEMS : Faster Internet

 At KEMS, we are committed to protect the privacy & security of your information upon visiting our website or registering your information which we collect & use to improve our services and further develop in understanding how we can serve your needs. This policy applies for future pages added on the website as well.

   Kindly go through KEMS’s Privacy Policy for further information. KEMS has the right to renew- add on to the content of this policy as necessary, so make sure you revisit it from time to time for future updates.

** Our Privacy Policy requirements include : **

·     Personal data, which will help us identify users.

·     How gathered data and information will be processed.

·     Parties allowed – responsible to process gathered data in complete confidentiality.

·     Authorized personnel to access the gathered data.

·     Explanation of available methodology for users and visitors of data collection, data use as well as data distribution.

·     How KEMS’s website handles registered users and visitors data.

·     Waving liability of data registered at other included websites.

** Personal data, which will help us identify users : **

We are only interested of gathering your personal information which will help us identify individual clients and our website is mostly accessed and browsed without the need of filling personal information. Such type of information is only required while placing an order for our services via our website such as name, address, contact details or email address, so clients can rest assure that those details will not be shared with a third party only for certain exceptions. 

** How gathered data and information will be processed : **

KEMS does not sell, share or distribute information to any party unless some technical or administrative processing is required and those as well are not allowed to share or sell them.   

** Parties allowed – responsible to process gathered data in complete confidentiality :  **

Data registered on KEMS’s website is secure and confidential; No one besides the company is allowed to access them. 

** Authorized personnel to access the gathered data : **

KEMS’s database if highly confidential, no one is granted access to them and they can’t be  disclosed  to outside parties except after obtaining a legal consent.

** Explanation of available methodology for users and visitors of data collection, data use as well as data distribution : **

Certain details some of which are essential while others lack importance will be sent to the company by an email message by the client or any others means applied. Upon successfully registering on the website for a domain name or hosting service, the user is asked to specify his needs or acquiring more information on the company by email. Gathered data will not be added to any mailing list unless client checks this option. 

** How KEMS’s website handles registered users and visitors data : **

KEMS secures the confidentiality of information provided by users on its website by processing it internally as need requires but we shall not be held responsible for transactions the user chooses to perform online fully by taking risk of offering complete personal data on the web. 

** Waving liability of data registered at other included websites : **

KEMS’s website includes links to outside website which the company will not be responsible for its content or privacy – security policy of them.
